Good Morning!
Good Morning. Good Morning. It is a new dawn.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Hallelujah!
I know your faith is lifted up.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
There is no way our faith can be lifted up without repentance.
Do you know that?
The Bible says that sin is never covered by our appearance.
This is what we believe today.
Sin is never covered by our appearance
Tell your neighbour.
[Sin is never covered by our appearance.]
Wrong is never covered by our prayer.
Prayer without repentance - we are talking to the air,
you are just making noise.
Tell your neighbour.
Our wrong, our sin, our mistake is never covered by our prayer.
I mean, prayer without repentance is never covered by our tears.
Sin can only be removed by repentance.
Wrong can only be removed by repentance.
And what is repentance? Simple.
You begin to step into repentance when you stop blaming others.
Your business is not good, you say, "Oh, it's witchcraft.
That is how it happened to our family -
my brother is not making it, my sister is not making it".
But when you are making it, when business is good, you say, "It's my hard working.
I am a graduate, I am a professor".
The SCOAN Sunday Service
When the goings are good, and you are making it, business is flourishing,
you say, "Oh my God, I wake up early in the morning, I clicked to my business".
You know what I am talking about.
But when business is bad, you begin to look for witches.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
You decide not to go home; you abandon your village because business is not going.
They are the ones haunting you.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Repentance comes when we stop blaming others
Tell your neighbour.
[Repentance comes when we stop blaming others.]
I can't hear you.
When it happens to you, you say, "Yes" - reproach
because of the pain you are going through.
Who is going through the pain? Is it witchcraft?
What you are going through, who is going through it? Is it wizard?
It is you that is going through the pain.
Tell your neighbour, "Repentance comes when you stop blaming others".
"I have been married for many years, no child, I have been barren.
Things have been very difficult. It is the same thing with my brothers at home.
This is trouble in the family."
You are shifting the blame.
But when things are good, you say it's your work.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Sin can only be removed by repentance.
It must be brought to the Blood of Jesus before the Spirit prays through us.
Our situation to where?
I can't hear you.
[Blood of Jesus.]
It must be brought to the Blood of Jesus before the Spirit prays through us.
The Blood of Jesus
The Blood of Jesus sets me free
From sin and sorrow
The Blood of Jesus
The Blood of Jesus sets me free
From sin and sorrow
It must be brought to the Blood of Christ before the Spirit prays through us.
We don't know how to pray; the Spirit prays.
MESSAGE TITLE: REPENTANCE
What do you think can hold you back?
Pain of the past, anger, hurt of the past - deep hurt.
"The man came from the village, the boy came from the village, the lady came from the village.
I homed him, I homed her. He lived with me.
I trained him, I sent him to university.
I trained him. Now he is a millionaire but he abandoned me.
He refused to pay me back. I will not forgive him."
The SCOAN Sunday Service
There is a lot of issue with you and your people.
"I trained him. He is the head of the company but he refuses to hear from me again."
This pain of the past.
In your spirit now you rise and say to the Lord:
Give me the Grace to forget the pain of the past and be kind to those who hurt me.
Say it again.
Lord, give me the grace to forget the pain of the past, injustice of the past,
cheats of the past and to be kind to those who hurt me.
Oh my God, you are hurt. You have been cheated.
These are the things that are holding you back.
Oh, they sacked you, injustice, sacked you without pay,
even unnoticed sack letter after serving for many years.
You say, "No, this is injustice you will never forget and forgive".
You must forgive.
This is what is holding you back.
"No! My wife, my husband threw my things out after building his career and his future.
Now he is a rich man. Look, he married a new wife.
And here I am out there. I will never forgive this man."
These are the things that are holding you back.
"Oh, I can never. This is so painful. I hate him."
"I brought him up. See today, he is calling me wizard, witch. I can never..."
These are the things that are holding you back.
See Jesus - "Father, forgive them."
The SCOAN Sunday Service
He loves me
I cannot say why
On Calvary Tree
He suffered for me
He loves me
I cannot say why
The SCOAN Sunday Service
What you have forgotten is that
God often uses circumstances of life to preserve us.
Those things you see as pain, cheating, injustice -
God often uses them to preserve us, to keep us, to train us, to rebuild us but we don't know.
Are you with me?
God often uses circumstances of life.
You have been praying to be this, to be a senator, to be a president, to be that.
If you had been a president, who knows what would have happened to you?
The SCOAN Sunday Service
What you have been praying for in the past,
if your prayer had been answered, who knows what would have happened to you?
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Ask your neighbour:
What I have been praying for in the past - fasting and praying -
if my prayer had been answered, who knows what would have happened?
The SCOAN Sunday Service
God often uses circumstance of life.
And what are the circumstances?
What you see as injustice, hate, cheating, pain.
"This is embarrassment, this is cheating - he cheated me!"
The SCOAN Sunday Service
"He sacked me, unnoticed, after serving for many years which is injustice."
Sometimes, God uses this kind of situation to preserve, to keep us for a new level
and to prepare us for a bright future.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Rise up right now. Let us pray for the viewers.
Let us open our lips, ask God to help us.
Give us the grace, Lord, to forget the pain of the past.
Pain can be this, can be that, can be injustice -
whatever pain, to forget the pain of the past.
Not only to forget the pain of the past - to be kind to those who hurt us in the past.
Open your lips, ask God
Give me the grace, Lord - grace to forget the pain of the past,
grace to forget the injustice of the past and to be kind to those who hurt me.
Prayer!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
You are released from the pain, in the name of Jesus.
Right now, open your lips.
Ask Him to give you the grace to live according to His Word.
That is the only way to maintain what you have received.
If you know you have received, you need maintenance.
Give me the grace to live according to Your Word.
Your Word says, "Thou shall not kill, thou shall not lie, thou shall not steal, thou shall not destroy."
Give me the grace, Lord, to live according to your Word.
If you know your life has been fixed, right now, ask for grace to live according to His Word.
Open your lips.
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
I can't hear you.
[Amen!]
Hallelujah!
I want to rejoice with you!
I know why I am rejoicing with you - I am in the midst of...
successful people!
I said it.
Whether you like it or not, you are a successful person!
Stretch your hand and pray for your nation, your country,
for unity among your leaders.
Prayer For The Nations
With Prophet T.B. Joshua
God intervention,
in Jesus Christ's name!
Right now, your journey.
God owns our future.
Ask God to give you the grace to continue the journey - journey of righteousness,
purity, holiness, faithfulness.
Ask God for the grace to be kind to those who hurt you.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Ask for the grace.
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
TT Monica Asefa 06/02/19
RV: Mel Flowers 21/02/2019